There are a thousand ways to raise your adrenaline. Today,
Chev Chelios will need every single one.
Crank is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Brian Taylor.
Chev Chelios, a hit man wanting to go straight,
lets his latest target slip away.
Then he awakes the next morning to a phone call that informs him he has been poisoned and has only an hour to
live unless he keeps adrenaline coursing through his body while he searches for an antidote.
Chev Chelios, played by Jason Statham.
Eve, played by Amy Smart.
Ricky Verona, played by Jose Pablo Cantillo.
Kaylo, played by Efren Ramirez.
Doc Miles, played by Dwight Yoakam.
Carlito, played by Carlos Sanz.
Crank is a 2006 American action film directed by Mark Neveldine
and Brian Taylor (in their directorial debut).
It stars Jason Statham, Amy Smart, Jose Pablo
Cantillo, Efren Ramirez and Dwight Yoakam.
In the film, Chev Chelios (Statham), an LA–based British assassin, is poisoned by a synthetic drug and must keep his adrenaline
flowing constantly to keep himself alive, while trying to track down the culprits responsible for poisoning him.
It was followed by a sequel titled Crank: High Voltage.
The film explores themes of assassin, helicopter, hitman, poison, fistfight.
The tone is intense.